A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Vice Presidential, Series 6 FA459
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Vice Presidential, 6
  - Contact Sheets, 1973-1977; 1
    - G1230 - G1232 - Boca Rotan, Florida. VP Rockefeller addresses the Young Presidents' Organization on the need to exercise their skills in the business and public sectors, 1975 April 19; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1233 - Boca Rotan, Florida. VP Rockefeller addresses the Young Presidents' Organization on the need to exercise their skills in the business and public sectors, 1975 April 22; Color (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1234 - Author Samuel Schoenbaum presents V.P. Rockefeller with the first edition of A Documentary Life of William Shakespeare" for the White House Library ", 1975 April 23; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1235 - The Vice President's Office. The VP meets with Valentin Berezkhov, 1975 April 23; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1236 - The State Department. VP Rockefeller addresses the National Advertising Council on the importance of relations with business and government, 1975 April 23; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1237 - VP Rockefeller meets with Insurance Investment Officer in his conference, 1975 April 23; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1238 - VP meets with Senator Beall and Senator Gude of Maryland to discuss the Washington Metro Subway System, 1975 April 23; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1239 - G1240 - The State Department. VP Rockefeller addresses the National Advertising Council on the importance of relations with business and government, 1975 April 23; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1241 - The Sheraton Park Hotel. VP Rockefeller presents the Marconi Award at the National Association of Engineers Banquet, 1975 April 23; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1242 - Terry O'Donnell Office. VP Rockefeller chats with OMB Directors James Lynn and Paul O'Neill and Jim Cannon, 1975 April 23; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1243 - The Oval Office. VP Rockefeller confers with President Ford, Secretary Kissinger and National Security Advisor Brent Scowcroft, 1975 April 23; Color (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1244 - Cabinet Room. VP Rockefeller chats with members of the National Security Council, 1975 April 24; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1245 - VP Office. VP Rockefeller meets with General Goodpaster. Cabinet Room. VP Rockefeller chats with members of the National Security Council, 1975 April 24; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1246 - Publication Portraits. Joseph Persico, Speech Writer for the VP. Thaddeus Garrett, Assistant to the VP for Urban Affairs, 1975 April 24; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1247 - NAR, Ambassador Symington and Senator Percy (IL) dine in Percy's home, 1975 April 25; Color (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1248 - The Home of Senator Charles Percy (R - Ill.). VP Rockefeller and Ambassador Symington dine with Sen. Percy, 1975 April 25; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1250 - The Cabinet Room. VP Rockefeller chats with members of the Cabinet following an Economic and Energy meeting with the President., 1975 April 25; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1257 - Thaddeus Garrett, Assistant to the Vice President for Urban Affairs, 1975 April 30; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1258 - VP with Egyptian Delegation. EOB Conf. Room, 1975 May 1; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1259 - G1260 - VP attends Swearing-In Ceremony for Rogers Morton and speaks at The Urban Coalition" Luncheon in D.C. ", 1975 May 1; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1261 - VP visits Prime Minister of Tunisia at Blair House, 1975 May 1; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1262 - Blair House. VP Rockefeller drops by to pay greetings to His Excellency Hedi Nouira, Prime Minister of Tunisia, 1975 May 1; Color (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1263 - GRF at Marriott GOP reception, 1975 May 1; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1267 - 5-6, VP meeting with Dixie Lee Ray. 7-14, VP meeting with S. Dillon Ripley. 15-30, VP meeting with Carla Hills at HUD, 1975 May 1; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1268 - VP meeting with Dixie Lee Ray and Carla Hills, 1975 May 1; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1269 - G1270 - VP Rockefeller at the dinner for King Hussain, 1975 May 1; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1271 - Untitled, 1975 May 2; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1272 - Untitled, 1975 May 2; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1273 - Untitled, 1975 May 2; Color (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1274 - NAR portrait, 1975 May 5; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1275 - G1276 - Reception at Capitol Hill Club, 1975 May 6; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1277 - Mike Farrell group; Ray Shafer; Industrial Investors Institute luncheon, 1975 May 6; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1278 - G1280 - Happy Rockefeller at the Naval Observatory, 1975 May 7; Color (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1281 - Mrs. Happy Rockefeller at the new Vice President's residence, 1975 May 7; Color (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1282 - Untitled, 1975 May 7; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1283 - VP with Senator Baker, staff and Senator Griffin, 1975 May 7; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1284 - William and Ordway Burden; Australian Prime Minister Whitlam; Senators Tower (TX) and Church (ID), 1975 May 7; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1285 - Members of the Archives of American Art; Senators Tower (TX) and Church (ID), 1975 May 7; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1286 - Kenneth Keating funeral services, 1975 May 8; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1287 - Hugh Morrow's mother-in-law; Australian Minister Whitlam, Prime Minister of Singapore; Water Quality Commission Meeting, 1975 May 8; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1288 - Prime Minister of Singapore; Lew Lefkowitz; Senator Bellmon's residence (OK), 1975 May 8; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1289 - Water Quality Commission meeting, 1975 May 8; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1290 - G1291 - Warm Springs, Virginia, 1975 May 9; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1292 - G1294 - The Museum of Modern Art. VP and Mrs. Rockefeller attend the dedication ceremony for the new MOMA galleries honoring A. H. Barr and Rene d'Harnoncourt, 1975 May 14; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1295 - The Cabinet Room. VP Rockefeller attends a meeting with President Ford to discuss New York State's financial problems with Mayor Beame and Governor Carey, 1975 May 14; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1296 - The U.S. Senate. VP Rockefeller greets his granddaughter Jennifer Rockefeller and the pupils from Pound Ridge Elementary School. Tom Korologos, 1975 May 14; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1297 - The U.S. Senate. VP Rockefeller meets with His Excellency Corneliu Bogdan, Ambassador of Romania, 1975 May 14; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1298 - The U.S. Senate, S-207. VP Rockefeller attends a drop-by meeting of Michigan Businessmen hosted by Senator Robert P. Griffin, 1975 May 14; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1299 - The Capitol Hill Club. VP Rockefeller attends a Businessmen Luncheon hosted by Congressman John W. Wydler (R - N.Y.), 1975 May 14; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 10, Volume 5)
    - G1300 - The U.S. Senate. VP Rockefeller greets his granddaughter Jennifer Rockefeller and the pupils from Pound Ridge Elementary School. Tom Korologos, 1975 May 14; Color (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1301 - The VP's Conference Room. The VP holds a staff meeting on Urban Affairs, 1975 May 14; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1302 - G1304 - The Smithsonian Institution, Regent's Room. VP Rockefeller attends the Board of Regents meeting., 1975 May 14; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1305 - The VP Conference Room. VP Rockefeller meets with the Longshoremen's Union President Henry Brydges, Nicki Brydges and William Chester with Vic. Borella, 1975 May 15; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1306 - The Blair House. VP Rockefeller makes a courtesy call on their Majesties The Shahanshah of Iran and the Empress Farah, 1975 May 15; Color (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1307 - G1308 - The Mayflower Hotel. VP Rockefeller addresses the National Republican Heritage Groups Council Luncheon, 1975 May 16; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1309 - The VP's Office. VP Rockefeller meets with Susan Schiffer, White House Fellow assigned to the Vice President, 1975 May 17; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1310 - G1315 - The Kennedy Center and the Embassy of Iran. Their Majesties the Shahanshah of Iran and the Empress Farah entertain VP and Mrs. Rockefeller, 1975 May 17; Color (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1316 - G1322 - Pocantico Hills -Tarrytown, N.Y. VP and Mrs. Rockefeller entertain the Shahanshah of Iran and the Empress Farah, 1975 May 18; Color (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1323 - G1325 - The Rayburn Office Bldg. - Room B-338. VP Rockefeller addresses the Congressional Black Caucus Forum on Full Employment, 1975 May 20; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1326 - VP Office. VP Rockefeller chats with Dr. William Teller and Berent Friel. VP Rockefeller presents the Blind with awards for their outstanding achievements, 1975 May 21; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1327 - The VP's Office. Victor Borella introduces Edward Kiernan, Howard Morse and Ken McFeeley of the International Conf. of Police Assn. to Rockefeller, 1975 May 21; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1328 - G1330 - The Renwick Art Gallery. VP and Mrs. Rockefeller host a dinner in the honor of retiring OAS Secretary-General Galo Plaza and his wife, 1975 May 22; Color (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1331 - G1332 - U.S. Capitol - The Old U.S. Supreme Court. Vice President attends the opening of the Old U.S. Supreme Court., 1975 May 22; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1333 - G1335 - Pocantico Hills, Tarrytown, N.Y. VP and David Rockefeller entertain his Excellency Leopold Sedar Senghor, President of Senegal and his wife Colette, 1975 May 23; Color (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1337 - G1339 - Pocantico Hills, Tarrytown, N.Y. VP and David Rockefeller entertain his Excellency Leopold Sedar Senghor, President of Senegal and his wife Colette, 1975 May 23; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1340 - 2-6 Meeting with Task Group on Drugs. 7-11 Meeting with representatives of National Home Builders Assn, 1975 May 28; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1341 - 7-22 Swearing-in of William Lane as Ambassador to the International Ocean Exposition, 23-31 Meeting with representatives of the National Home Builders Assn, 1975 May 28; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1342 - 7-11 Briefing by Dick Parson on Drugs, 12-19 Swearing-in of William Lane as Ambassador to the International Ocean Exposition, 20-24 Mtg. on Privacy Committee, 1975 May 28; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1344 - 2a-3a Robert Seamans and Jim Cannon, 4a-11a His Excellency James C.H. Shen, Ambassador of the Republic of China, 12a-15a White House Fellows Reunion --450 EOB, 16a-30a Romanian--US Economic Council Reception, 1975 May 29; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1345 - 2-5 Bill Whyte, 6-11 Jack Marsh and Jim Cannon, 12-16 Robert Seamans and Jim Cannon, 17-25 His Excellency James C.H. Shen, Ambassador of the Republic of China, 26-32 Meeting with Imperial Iranian National Defense Univ. Faculty and Students, 1975 May 29; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1346 - 2a-14a White House Fellows Reunion, Room 450 EOB, 15a-21a General Clarke Henry Diamond and Jim Smith, 22a-26a Frank Zarb, 27a-28a Joe Canzarie and Shirley Browne, 29a-33a Romanian-US Economic Council Reception, 1975 May 29; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1347 - VP briefing Press on CIA Report and meeting of the Commission, 1975 June 2; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1348 - VP briefing Press on CIA Report, 1975 June 2; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1349 - 3-13 VP Zarb and Morton, 14-18 Heath Larry, 1975 June 3; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 11, Volume 6)
    - G1350 - G1355 - VP's Participation in Graduation Exercises at US Naval Academy, Annapolis, Maryland, 1975 June 4; Color (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1356 - The VP aboard Marine II enroute Annapolis, Maryland, 1975 June 4; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1357 - Meeting with Frank Zarb, Roger Morton, Bill Seidman and James Cannon, 1975 June 5; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1358 - 3-10 VP meets with Anura Bandaranaik, 11-32 Bi-Partisan Meeting in the Cabinet Room, 33-36 Dave Rays relatives, 1975 June 5; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1358a - The Vice President attends FIAB Luncheon at the Blair House, 1975 June 5; Color (Volume 6)
    - G1359 - 2 Ambassador Ramsbotham, 3 Shirley Browne, 4-11 Ambassador Bunker, 12-13 Doug Bennett, 14-21 Birthday Party for Shirley Browne, 1975 June 5; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1360 - Meetings with Ambassador Ramsbotham, John McGoff and Doug Bennett, 1975 June 5; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1361 - 3-18 The VP meets with the Science Advisory Committee at the Capitol, 19-27 VP meets with the President in the Oval Office, 1975 June 5; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1362 - Untitled (GRF and Mrs. Ford), 1975 June 5; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1363 - The President and VP greets Members of the CIA Commission, 1975 June 5; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1364 - The VP meets with the Science Advisory Committee at the Capitol, 1975 June 10; Color (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1365 - The Vice President attends FIAB Luncheon at the Blair House, 1975 June 5; Color (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1366 - G1367 - National Press Building --Sigma Delta Chi Reception and Dinner, 1975 June 6; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1368 - Meeting with Frank Zarb, Roger Morton, Bill Seidman and James Cannon, 1975 June 5; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1369 - The Vice President at the Capitol with Senators Javits and Percy, 1975 June 10; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1370 - G1371 - RHOB 2318. Testimony before House Science and Technology Committee and Domestic Council Meeting - Cabinet Room, 1975 June 10; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1372 - Oval Office - The Vice President presents to the President the CIA Report, 1975 June 10; Color (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1373 - 2a-6a Taking Oath and Signing Passport, 7a-23a CIA Commission Staff, 24a-28a Mr. Wagonseller, National Chairman of the American Legion, 1975 June 11; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1374 - The Vice President and Senator Hanson congratulate Secretary Hathaway on his confirmation, Robert Goheen, 1975 June 11; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1375 - 2-5 Senator Hanson, 6-9 Senator Biden and guest Eunice Gilroy, 10-13 Maggie Heghes and son Tom, 14-18 Republican Pages, 19-21 Democratic Pages, 22-26 Governor Hathaway, 1975 June 11; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1376 - The Vice President's trip to New York Republican State Dinner held at the Waldorf Astoria, 1975 June 12; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1377 - Re-enlistment of Sargent William Moore and various shots aboard Air Force 2, 1975 June 12; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1378 - Re-enlistment of Sargent William Moore and various shots aboard Air Force 2, 1975 June 12; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1379 - G1381 - The Vice President's trip to New York Republican State Dinner held at the Waldorf Astoria, 1975 June 12; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1382 - The Vice President (head shots), 1975 June 12; Color (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1383 - The Vice President meets with Deans of seven Michigan Universities, 1975 June 16; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1384 - 2a-6a Vice President with Carla Hill and Phil Buchen, 7a-13a Secretary General Waldheim, 14a-15a President Scheel of Germany and Speaker Albert, 16a-19a Senator Glenn, 20a-25a Sir Walter Perry, 26a-30a Gino Palucci, 1975 June 17; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1385 - 2-3 Jack Marsh, 4 Elizabeth MacBeth, 5-7 Visitors at the Capitol, 8-10 Secretary General Waldheim, 11-13 Vice President, 14-15 Senator John Glenn, 1975 June 17; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1386 - G1387 - 2500 Foxhall -Dinner for former Governors, 1975 June 17; Color (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1388 - 2-5 President's Panel on Federal Compensation, 6-12 Senator Brock and Senator Baker, 13-16 Secretary Dunlop, 17-21 Maritime briefing, 22-25 Robert Ellsworth, Asst. Secretary of Defense, 1975 June 18; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1389 - Mrs. Ford at Republican Luncheon 0-8a, Vice President with Rowland Evans 9-12, Vice President with Charlie Sandman 13-17, Vice President with Ned Reagan 18-20, Vice President with Rov Innis, Cyril Goodrich, Ed Brown, Mr. Boybness 21-25, 1975 June 23; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1390 - 0-3 Mrs. Ford at Republican Luncheon, 4-7 Vice President with Ned Reagan, 1975 June 23; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1391 - 4-8 Barry Goldwater, 9-11 Charlie Sandman, 12-20 Ned Reagan, 1975 June 23; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1392 - 2-6 Capitol Hill pics, 7-12 Rowland Evans, 13-16 Charlie Sandman, 17-19 Ned Reagan, 1975 June 23; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1393 - G1394 - Opening performance of the Metropolitan Opera's week at Wolf Trap Farm, 1975 June 23; Color (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1395 - OAS Dinner, 1975 June 24; Color (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1396 - Vice President with National Commission on Productivity and Work Quality 4-7, General Goodpasture, GRF, Oval Office 8-28, Dixie Lee Ray 29-33, 1975 June 25; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1397 - Vice President with National Commission on Productivity and Work Quality 5-7, President and General Andrew J. Goodpasture 8-10, 1975 June 25; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1399 - Staff Meeting and Lunch 0-6, Cabinet Meeting 7-10, Barbara Walters 12-18, GRF Press Conference 11-28, 1975 June 25; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 12, Volume 6)
    - G1400 - GRF Press Conference - South Lawn, 1975 June 25; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1401 - Staff Meeting 0-6, Lunch 7-10, Cabinet Meeting 11-16, Vice President with Barbara Walters, 17-34, 1975 June 25; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1402 - Reception for Republican National Associates (page 1), 1975 June 25; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1402a - Reception for Republican National Associates (page 2), 1975 June 25; Black and White (Volume 7)
    - G1403 - Staff Meeting, 1975 June 25; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1404 - Staff Meeting, Lunch, 1975 June 25; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1405 - Staff Meeting, 1975 July 3; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1406 - G1407 - Vice President at airport - Europe arrival, 1975 July 8; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1408 - G1417, G1419 - G1422 - The Vice President in Atlanta, Georgia for hearings with the National Commission on Water Quality, 1975 July 9; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1423 - Return Flight from Atlanta, Georgia aboard AF #2 and Staff Meeting with Morrow, Herter, Allison, Veneman, and Shafer, 1975 July 10; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1424 - 2-5 Republican State Chairman from the State of Georgia, 6-8 Paris-Match Reporter, Ms. Palacci, 1975 July 10; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1425 - 3-7 The Vice President and Senator Javits, 8-11 Col. Jack Walker, Joe Duncan and Dick Allison, 1975 July 11; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1426 - Staff Meeting and Departure for New York from Andrews Air Force Base, 1975 July 11; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1427 - G1428 - Award Ceremony for Col. Jack Walker and Family, 1975 July 14; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1429 - 3-13 Geridee Wheeler and Bill McFadzean, 14-32 Surprise Birthday Party for President Ford in the East Room, 1975 July 14; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1430 - Lunch with Morton, Levi, Lynn, Hills, Allison, Shafer, Mitchell, Cannon, Seidman, Meeting with Seamans, 1975 July 14; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1431 - Staff Meeting - Morrow, Herter, Allison, Veneman, Shafer, 1975 July 14; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1432 - G1433 - The Vice President and Bo Callaway and Water Quality Commission Picnic, 1975 July 15; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1434 - Water Quality Commission Picnic at 2500 Foxhall, 1975 July 15; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1435 - Frank Zarb, Water Quality Committee Meeting, Executive Commission on Federal Compensation, 1975 July 15; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1436 - Picnic for Water Quality Commission, Foxhall Rd., 1975 July 15; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1437 - Picnic for Water Quality Commission, Foxhall Rd., 1975 July 15; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1438 - Water Quality Committee Meeting and Foxhall Rd. Picnic for Committee, 1975 July 15; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1439 - Water Quality Commission picnic at Foxhall, 1975 July 15; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1440 - National Youth Camp Meeting with Senator Jennings Randolph, 1975 July 16; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1441 - National Youth Camp Meeting, Meeting F. David Matthews - HEW, 1975 July 16; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1442 - G1443 - National Youth Camp Meeting, Dirksen Office Building, 1975 July 16; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1444 - G1446 - Meeting of Science and Technology Consultants, Conference Room, 1975 July 17; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 13, Volume 7)
    - G1447 - G1454 - Staff Picnic at the Vice President's residence, 2500 Foxhall, 1975 July 17; Color (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1455 - Admiral's House, 1975 July 18; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1456 - Admiral's House, 1975 July 18; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1457 - Admiral's House, 1975 July 18; Color (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1458 - Admiral's House, 1975 July 18; Color (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)
    - G1459 - 3-9 Dennis Farley, Wall Street Journal, 10-14 Susan Herter and Bob Armao, 15-17 Economic Mtg., 18 Judy Harbaugh, 1975 July 18; Black and White (Box 4, Folder 14, Volume 7)